Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/surbhisharma-34b8741b4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Human Resources (HR)

Recruiting

Hiring

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Oracle Solaris Cluster 3.2 System Administrator Certified Professional

IBM Certified Advanced Database Administrator - DB2 10.1 for Linux UNIX and Windows

Certified Outsourcing Specialist: Human Resources (COS)

Oracle Data Integrator 11g Certified Implementation Essentials

Microsoft Server Virtualization with Windows Server Hyper-V and System Center

Surbhi Sharma

Software Engineer | HR Management | Talent Acquisition Head | Ex-Google

Delhi

Summary

Software support specialist with 5+ years of experience in providing support and assistance to clients, managing user accounts, and recruiting and hiring new IT support interns. Built customer relationships and trust with 20+ B2B clients. Talented in simplifying complex problems, making it easy for non-technical specialists to solve IT issues.

Experience

Microsoft

Talent Acquisition Specialist August 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Google

Database Administrator
July 2015 - July 2017 (2 years 1 month)

Karnataka, India

Education

Delhi University

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Information

Technology · (2012 - 2015)